salesbacker.com 2016-04-17

# Privacy Policy

Effective date: June 3, 2015

This website is owned and operated by Salesbacker LLC, doing business as Salesbacker (“Salesbacker”). Throughout the website, the terms “Salesbacker,” “we,” “us” and “our” refer to Salesbacker. This **Privacy Policy** applies to information that users transmit to the Salesbacker website at www.salesbacker.com (the “Site”).

We are committed to your privacy. This Privacy Policy informs you about the information we collect from you on our Site and how we and our affiliates use that information.

##  Identity and access

When you sign up for Salesbacker, we ask for personal information such as your name and email address. That’s just so you can personalize your new account, and we can send you updates, email alerts that you subscribe to, or other essential information. We’ll never sell your personal info to third parties, and we won’t use your name in marketing statements without your permission.

We log access to all accounts by IP address, so we can verify that no unauthorized access has happened for as long as the logs are kept.

When you write Salesbacker with a question or to ask for help, we’ll keep that correspondence, and the email address, for future reference. When you browse our marketing pages, we’ll track that for statistical purposes (like conversion rates and to test new designs). We also store any information you volunteer, like surveys, for as long as it makes sense.

The only times we’ll ever share your info:

  * To provide products or services you’ve requested, with your permission.
  * To investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
  * If Salesbacker is acquired by or merged with another company, we’ll notify you well before any info about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

##  Cookies and Web Server Logs

Like many websites, we use cookies and other standard web technology to collect information for our own use. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s internet browser for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make the online experience easier and more personalized. Information gathered through cookies and web server log files may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, IP addresses, links to/from any page, and time spent on the Site. Log files are used to monitor, measure, analyze, improve, and troubleshoot our services. You can choose to disable cookies for our Site but this may limit your ability to use our Site and services.

##  Facebook Custom Audience Advertisements

We may display interest-based ads to you when you are using Facebook, through Facebook’s Custom Audience Tool. This tool allows us to personalize our ads based on your visits to our website, and based on your email address. Aside from your email address, we do **not** share any of your other personal information with Facebook. We also do **not** share any product, order, customer, or other information that we may have imported to your Salesbacker subscriber account, if any. We simply use this tool to present offers to you that we believe may be of interest to you, based on your prior visit(s).

##  Law enforcement

Salesbacker won’t hand your data over to law enforcement unless a court order says we have to. We reject requests from local and federal law enforcement when they seek data without a court order. And unless we’re legally prevented from it, we’ll always inform you when such requests are made.

##  Encryption

Sensitive data is encrypted via [SSL/TLS](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transport_Layer_Security) when transmitted from our servers to your browser. Sensitive data in our database is also encrypted, for example, your account password.

When you sign up for one of our paid Plans, we use [Stripe Payments](https://stripe.com/about) to process your credit card information. Your credit card information never touches our servers. It is sent directly to Stripe, who guards it using the [most stringent levels of security available](https://stripe.com/help/security). We do store your billing zip code, which we are required to collect for accounting purposes.

##  Changes and questions

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time as our services change and grow. All amendments will be automatically effective 30 days after they are posted on the Site. The most current version of the Privacy Policy can be found at <https://www.salesbacker.com/privacy>.

Please direct any questions about this Privacy Policy to us through our [Contact form](https://www.salesbacker.com/contact) at <https://www.salesbacker.com/contact>.
